// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options and answers

let questions = [
   {
     numb: 1,
     question: "The series Friends is set in which city?",
     answer: "New York City",
     options: [
         "Los Angeles",
         "New York City",
         "Miami",
         "Seattle"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 2,
     question: "What is Monica skilled at?",
     answer: "Cooking",
     options: [
         "Singing",
         "American football",
         "Cooking",
         "Bricklaying"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 3,
     question: "Monica briefly dates billionaire Pete Becker. Which country does he take her for their first date??",
     answer: "Italy",
     options: [
         "France",
         "England",
         "Greece",
         "Italy"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 4,
     question: "What’s the name of the 1950s-themed diner where Monica worked as a waitress?",
     answer: "Moondance Diner",
     options: [
         "Marilyn & Audrey",
         "Moondance Diner",
         "Twilight Galaxy",
         "Marvin’s"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 5,
     question: "What’s the name of Janice’s first husband??",
     answer: "Gary Litman",
     options: [
         "Gary Litman",
         "Sid Goralnik",
         "Rob Bailystock",
         "Nick Layster"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "What job does Ross have??",
     answer: "Paleontologist",
     options: [
         "Paleontologist",
         "Artist",
         "Photographer",
         "Insurance salesman"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 7,
     question: "What’s the name of Joey’s penguin?",
     answer: "Huggsy",
     options: [
         "Snowflake",
         "Waddle",
         "Huggsy",
         "Bobber"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 8,
     question: "What is Chandler’s middle name?",
     answer: "Muriel",
     options: [
         "Jason",
         "Kim",
         "Zachary",
         "Muriel"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 9,
     question: "What is Janice most likely to say?",
     answer: "Oh… my… God!",
     options: [
         "Talk to the hand!",
         "Get me a coffee!",
         "Oh… my… God!",
         "No way!"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 10,
     question: "Who sang the Friends theme?",
     answer: "The Rembrandts",
     options: [
         "The Da Vinci Band",
         "The Rembrandts",
         "The Constables",
         "The Banksys"
     ]

   }



];
